Again I open the tales of the Papuan peoples of New Guinea, those who are closely related to it.
There are many interesting facts about the character of Orlin and about the long flight.
You will find there not difficult, which can be surprised, about the girls who work, who get married early,
only there it is not a joke, if the husband is a slave.
About the thick starchy sea and about the lonely grief.
About the distant bare reefs and about the myths, that from where,
how the flour is crushed by the moon and about the lunar flight of Geba.
Bread with agave on the essence, in the birds of paradise everywhere,
about the walking trees, about the beliefs about the fire and about the sun's heat from the sky,
even if I have never been there, I open the tales again.