Again I open the fairy tales of the Papuan people,
born in New Guinea, those who are closely related to her.
There are many interesting facts about the character of the eagle and about the long flight.
You will not find it difficult there, which can be surprised,
about the girls working, going to get married early,
only there is no joke, if the husband is a joker.
About the thick starched sea and about the lonely mountains,
about the distant bare reefs and about the myths, what from where,
how they beat the flour to the moons, and about the lunar escape of the geba,
about the bread with agave in the essence, about the birds of paradise everywhere,
about the walking trees, about the beliefs about the fire and about the heat of the sun from the sky,
let me never have been there, I open the fairy tales again.