I open fairy tales again, Papuans of those peoples from New Guinea, those who are closely connected with it.
There are many interesting facts about the character of the eagle and about the long flight.
You will find there not difficult to be surprised, about the working girls who get married early,
but there is no joke about the thick starch sea and about the lonely mountain,
about the distant bare reefs and about the myths of what and where,
how they beat the flour with a column and about the lunar escape of Geba,
about the bread with the agave, about the birds of paradise everywhere,
about the walking trees, about the beliefs about the fire and about the burning of the sun from the sky,
even though I have never been there.
I open fairy tales again.